<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>scripts on Kasual Komoroski</title><link>https://blog.komoro.ski/tags/scripts/</link><description>Recent content in scripts on Kasual Komoroski</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:20:21 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.komoro.ski/tags/scripts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Simple Bash Templating</title><link>https://blog.komoro.ski/2020/11/28/simple-bash-templating/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:20:21 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.komoro.ski/2020/11/28/simple-bash-templating/</guid><description>I needed to set up a project template which would be used to rapidly create many repositories with essentially the same skeleton boilerplate. I didn&amp;rsquo;t need much more than simple find replace, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t need the robust features of an entire templating engine &amp;ndash; just something simple with little dependencies. No one will use a template if it takes hours to set up an environment to populate it. In my search, I came across great gnu util called envsubst which will replace any bash environment variables in a file and output the result to standard out.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Markdown Setup</title><link>https://blog.komoro.ski/2018/03/03/hugo-markdown-setup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 15:57:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.komoro.ski/2018/03/03/hugo-markdown-setup/</guid><description>Now with my blog set up, I thought I should share the set up I use script I use when writing blog posts (and maybe markdown pages in general).
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what Hugo is, I suggest you check it out. At its core a static site generator that takes markdown files and compiles them into static html files, but it does so much more. Packaged with the file compiler is a webserver that uses websockets to support a live reload feature.</description></item></channel></rss>