<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>devember on Kasual Komoroski</title><link>https://blog.komoro.ski/tags/devember/</link><description>Recent content in devember on Kasual Komoroski</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 18:16:49 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.komoro.ski/tags/devember/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improving My Network: Public Proxy and Wireguard VPN</title><link>https://blog.komoro.ski/2021/01/01/improving-my-network-public-proxy-and-wireguard-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 18:16:49 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.komoro.ski/2021/01/01/improving-my-network-public-proxy-and-wireguard-vpn/</guid><description>This is the third part in my series on taking the Devember challenge and improving my homelab and network. You can find the previous post here.
Unifi Dream Machine Pro Problems I upgraded my router to a Unifi Dream Machine Pro over the summer, which has treated me well, but running custom scripts and applications on the box has been a challenge because the UDM Pro will wipe out any customizations whenever a firmware upgrade is applied, and some changes get wiped out in a reboot.</description></item><item><title>Improving My Network: Domains and DNS</title><link>https://blog.komoro.ski/2020/12/22/improving-my-network-domains-and-dns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 22:35:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.komoro.ski/2020/12/22/improving-my-network-domains-and-dns/</guid><description>This is the second part in my series on taking the Devember challenge and improving my homelab and network. You can find the previous post here.
Domain The first step in re-vamping my homelab was to finally purchase a domain. I was a complete novice on domain, dns, and subnet management going into the challenge, so I asked some friends about it. Fortunately, the process was much simpler than I anticipated.</description></item><item><title>Improving My Network: A Messy Situation</title><link>https://blog.komoro.ski/2020/12/21/improving-my-network-a-messy-situation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 19:48:59 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.komoro.ski/2020/12/21/improving-my-network-a-messy-situation/</guid><description>In November 2020, I decided to take the Level 1 Techs Devember Challenge, which is a challenge for anyone to spend an hour a day working on a tech project. The challenge is sponsored by Linode, which offers some free credit for new users taking the challenge. I opted to take the challenge and finally buy a domain and set up my network properly. Since I&amp;rsquo;ve never had a domain before, my experience with proper networking and dns management were novice at best, so I figured it would take me plenty of time to get things setup.</description></item></channel></rss>